天呐
God.
猜猜谁今天会很棒
Guess who's about to have the best day ever?
会不会是那个
Could it be the fellow
刚刚大喊了一声  粗鲁地
who just interrupted us, rather rudely,
打断了我们的家伙
with "Booyah"?
怎么回事  老爸
What's going on, Dad?
对不起  不能告诉你们  我发誓保密了
I'm sorry. I can't tell you. I'm sworn to secrecy.
好吧  总之
Okay. Anyway.
-我的精神病学教授说恐惧是种情感  -嗯
- So my psych professor said fear is an emotion... - Yeah.
这没错  但我...
...which it is, but then I arg--
你都不打算撬撬我的嘴吗
You're not even gonna try to pry the secret out of me?
亲爱的  我俩正说话呢
Darling, we are right in the middle of something here,
你就等一会儿的
so if you just wait for a moment,
我们稍后会全力关注你的  好吗
we will give you our full attention, okay?
好了
Okay.
说吧  亲爱的
What is it, darling?
奶奶  你知道他不得逞
Gram, you know he's just gonna keep pouting
就会一直噘嘴
until he gets his way.
爸爸  把秘密说出来吧
Dad, just tell us your secret.
-好吧  但只是因为你们那么想知道  -好吧
- Okay, but only because you insisted. - Okay.
我刚跟人打完电话
I just got off the phone
跟我通话的是一位私人助理  他的老板是
with the personal assistant of none other than...
史蒂芬·金
Stephen King.
他来纽约看他的公寓
He's in town visiting his New York apartment,
打来是问我
has called to see if I'm available
有没有空见个面  商谈...戏剧化停顿
for a meeting to talk about a... dramatic pause...
合作
...collaboration.
等等  他不是还在为那事生气吗
Hold on. Isn't he still mad about the thing?
什么事
What thing?
棒球那事
The baseball thing.
史蒂芬·金是个红袜队的铁杆球迷
See, Stephen King is a huge Red Sox fan and...
而你父亲是洋基队的球迷
Oh, and your father is a Yankees fan.
糟糕  理查德  你做了什么
Oh, no, Richard. What did you do?
就是个无良的玩笑
It was a silly joke.
更像是半公开的威胁
More like a thinly veiled threat.
有什么区别
Tomato, to-mah-to.
显然那都是过去的事了
Obviously it's water under the bridge,
因为他想跟我讨论合作项目的事
because he wants to talk about collaborating on a project.
"理查德·卡塞尔和史蒂芬·金推出"
"Richard Castle and Stephen King present."
祝我好运吧  女士们
Wish me luck, ladies.
亲爱的  如果你觉得
Darling, if you think
你会排在史蒂芬·金前面
you're going to get top billing over Stephen King,
你需要的可不止运气
you're going to need more than luck.
-早上好  -早
- Good morning. - Morning.
早啊  警监
Morning, Captain.
蕾妮  你好吗
Hey, Lanie, how you doing?
比被害人好多了
A heck of a lot better than our victim here.
名叫艾玛·马修斯  34岁
Name is Emma Matthews, 34 years old,
上背一个枪伤
single GSW to the upper back...
穿透
through and through.
这是出口伤
Here's our exit wound.
从尸斑看
Based on lividity,
我认为死亡时间是
I'm placing the time of death between
昨晚9点到11点
9:00 and 11:00 last night.
邻居没听到枪声吗
And the neighbors didn't hear a gunshot?
没有  音乐被开得很大
No, the music was turned up too loud.
但隔壁邻居说
But the neighbor next door
死亡时间范围附近  看到外面停了一辆
said he saw a rusty, white van parked outside
锈迹斑斑的白货车  但没记住车牌
near the time-of-death window... didn't get a plate, though.
艾玛有室友吗
Does Emma have a roommate?
没有  独居
No. She lives alone.
但我们通知了近亲
But we've, uh, notified next of kin,
得到了朋友同事的名单
and we've got a list of her friends and co-workers.
艾玛是8频道新闻的一名电视制作人
Emma was a television producer at channel 8 news.
部分同事
Some of her co-workers
会去分局见我们
are gonna meet us back at the precinct.
那画的是什么
And what's with the artwork?
尚不清楚
Not sure yet,
但我们认为可能是凶手画的
but we think that our killer may have drawn it.
好吧  联系联调局
All right, check with the FBI,
看杀人手法或这个标志
see if the M.O. or if the symbol
是否在数据库中能找到
matches anything in their database.
贝克特
Hey, Beckett.
会面怎么样了
So, how's the meeting going?
史蒂芬还生你气吗
Is Stephen still mad at you?
我刚到
I just got here.
如果他不生我气了
And if he's not still mad at me,
等我叫他解雇了他的地产经纪人他也会生气的
he will be when I tell him to fire his real-estate agent.
好好的
Be nice.
是好好对史蒂芬还是来门口
What, to Stephen or to the team of rats
迎接我的一队老鼠啊
that came to welcome me at the door?
好了  我挂了  爱你
All right. I got to go. I love you.
史蒂芬  是你吗
Stephen, is that you?
我知道了  真逗
I get it. Very funny.
洋基队还是最棒的
Yeah, Yankees are still the best team...
莱恩  联调局有消息吗
Hey, Ryan, anything from the FBI?
没有  符号他们数据库里没有
No. The symbol's not in their database.
凶手杀人手法也没有
Neither is our killer's M.O.
艾玛公寓外那辆锈迹斑斑的
And what about the white, rusty van
白货车呢
outside of Emma's apartment?
查到了吗
You guys track it down?
她那个街区没有监控
No traffic cams on her block,
目前情况不妙
so so far it's not looking good.
伙计们
Hey, guys.
这都是艾玛的同事
These are Emma's co-workers.
利拉·坎波和詹妮弗·佩雷兹
This is Lila Campo and Jennifer Perez.
这位是我搭档  莱恩警探
This is my partner, Detective Ryan,
和我们上司  贝克特警监
and our boss, Captain Beckett.
节哀顺变
I'm sorry about your loss.
谢谢  警监  我们还没缓过来呢
Thank you, Captain. We are still in shock.
我们去这边谈
We're gonna talk over here.
请跟我来
Follow me, please.
莱恩  我一下午
Ryan, I'm gonna be at the
都要去参加鉴证科技研讨会
forensic technology seminar all afternoon.
有什么情况给我发短信  好吗
So just text me if anything comes up, okay?
-好的  警监  -谢谢
- Yeah, you got it, Cap. - Thanks.
天呐
Oh, my God.
那是艾玛的血吗
Is that Emma's blood?
是的
Yeah, I'm afraid so.
你们认得镜子上画的符号吗
Do you recognize the symbol drawn on the mirror?
我没见过
I've never seen it before.
我也是
Neither have I.
这难以置信
I mean, I just can't believe this.
艾玛是最可爱的人了
Emma... Emma was the sweetest person in the world.
她善良  开朗
I mean, she was kind, she was outgoing...
但她最近是有些怪怪的
though she had been acting a little strange lately.
怎么说
Strange how?
艾玛刚获得升职
Well, Emma had just gotten a promotion
去制作11点档新闻
to produce the 11:00 news.
这对她来说很重大
Which was a huge deal for her.
是啊
Exactly.
但她这一周都...
Yet all this week, she was acting kind of...
怎么说呢
I don't know.
-怪怪的  -是啊
- Off. - Yeah.
知道为什么吗
Well, any idea why?
艾玛跟我说
Well, Emma confided in me
她拿到了什么
that she had gotten her hands on
证明
some kind of proof.
什么的证明
Uh, proof of what?
她说不能告诉我
She said that she couldn't tell me,
至少得等到时机合适
at least not until after the time was right,
不知是什么意思
whatever that meant.
你们是否知道
Do either of you know
艾玛跟谁有什么私人恩怨吗
if Emma was having personal problems with anyone,
比如工作上或者生活上
anyone at work, in her personal life?
我是不知道
Not that I know of.
有巴克利
Well, there's Buckley.
是啊  但新闻编辑室的人
Yeah, but everybody in the newsroom
都对巴克利有问题
has problems with Buckley.
那是谁
Who's Buckley?
是电视台另一位制作人
Another producer at the station...
他比艾玛资历深
he had seniority over Emma,
但她却代替他升了职
but she beat him out for that promotion.
巴克利很不爽
And Buckley was pissed.
是啊  他甚至说
Yeah, I mean, he even claimed
她为了得到工作散布了他的谣言
that she'd made up lies about him just to get the job.
但我无法想象他会为此杀人
But I can't imagine he would kill her for that.
巴克利是否开一辆白色货车
By any chance, does Buckley drive a white van?
是的
Yeah, he does.
我又回幼儿园了吗
What, am I in kindergarten again?
芬奇老师呢
So where's Mrs. Finch?
你不是芬奇老师
You are not Mrs. Finch.
你们是谁
Who are you guys?
我在哪
Where am I?
我不知道
I don't know.
我和这人刚醒来
Me and this guy just woke up.
我的肩膀好疼
My shoulder's killing me.
有人有电话吗  我的不见了
Anyone have a phone? Mine's gone.
没有
No.
怎么回事
What the hell is going on?
我们怎么过来的
How did we get here?
我印象里最后一件事是去
Last thing I remember I-I went to a...
一栋破破烂烂的大楼见史蒂芬·金
a run-down building going to meet Stephen King
然后灯一盏盏熄灭了
and then all the lights went out.
等等  尼可拉斯街143号吗
Hold on... 143 Nicholas Street?
你怎么知道
How did you know that?
有个律师来电话  叫我去见他
A lawyer called, asked me to meet him there...
说我从一年前
said I inherited the building
去世的叔叔那里继承了这栋楼
from my uncle who passed away a year ago.
是啊  我也是收到了这样的消息
Yeah, I was told the same thing,
但说的是我几个月前
except it was supposedly my cousin
去世的堂亲
who died a few months ago.
天呐
Oh, my God.
我们都被骗了过去
We were all lured there.
可是谁呢
Yeah, but by whom?
我胳膊上有黏黏的东西
There's a sticky substance on my arms.
你们呢
Do you guys have that?
这东西撞不开
This thing's not budging.
好吧
Okay, um...
我在走廊里
You know, when I was in that hallway,
看着灯熄灭的时候
when the lights went out,
最后只记得肩膀一阵刺痛
last thing I remember was a sharp pain in my shoulder.
我们肯定是被人用注射器或麻醉针下药了
So we must have been drugged with a syringe or a tranq dart.
为什么啊  谁会这么对我们
But why? Who would do that to us?
我猜是那个镜头后的人
My guess is whoever's behind that camera.
天呐  是连环杀手
Oh, man, it's a serial killer.
我《日界线》上见过这种事的报道
I've seen stuff like this on "Dateline,"
从来没有好结局
and it never ends well.
你能不能闭嘴
Will you please shut the hell up?
我只是想告诉你
I'm just trying to tell you, this is a...
-闭嘴  -各位
- Shut up! - Guys...
不管是谁做的
whoever is behind this,
如果那人想要我们死  我们早死了
if they wanted us dead, we would be dead.
所以显然对方是另有所图
So, obviously, they want something else, right?
是啊  但什么呢
Yeah, b-but what?
我不知道
I don't know.
我们到处看看吧
Let's take a look around.
显然有人费心费力地
Obviously someone went through a lot of trouble
设计了这里
designing this place.
伙计们
Guys.
"拯救就在其中"
"Salvation lies within."
那是什么
What is that thing?
是密码筒
It's a cryptex.
是个上锁的盒子
It's kind of a lock box
需要密码才能开启
that requires a password to open it.
我们需要密码
So we just need the password.
我们得马上冲出去
We need to bust out of here... now.
刃是橡皮的
The blade's rubber.
那是蜜蜂吗
Is that a bee?
我过敏  我严重过敏
I'm allergic. I'm very allergic!
放松  你把它激怒了
Okay, well, relax. You're antagonizing it.
它好像被我胳膊上的东西吸引
I think it's attracted to the stuff that's on my arm.
不
Oh, no.
你没事吧
Are you all right?
好了  放松  放松
Okay, relax. Relax.
你要过敏性休克了
You're going into anaphylactic shock.
你有肾上腺素吗
Do you have epinephrine?
我的注射器没了  本来就在我兜里的
My injector's gone! It was in my pocket!
哪去了  哪去了
Where is it? Where is it?!
没事的  哥们
It's okay, man. It's okay.
我们会找到的
We'll find it.
伙计们  这上面有蜜蜂的图案
Guys, there's a picture of a bee.
或许你的肾上腺素在这里面
Maybe your epinephrine's in here.
我们怎么办
W-What should we do?
我们需要密码
We need the password.
呼吸  呼吸
Just breathe. Just breathe.
好吗  我们会想到办法的
All right? We'll figure this out.
各位  有几个字母上面有蜜蜂
Guys, some of the letters have little bees over them.
-阿戴  -怎么回事
- A-D-E... - What the hell?
-伊洛  -放松
- ...I-L-O... - Take it easy.
-好  -普莱
- Okay. - ...P, R, and Y.
什么意思
What does that mean?
不知道  可能是个词  或是短语
I don't know. It could be a word, maybe it's a phrase.
"牛奶杆"  不对
Uh, "Dairy pole"... no.
"我玩实干家"
"I play doer."
"可怕的策略"
"A dire ploy."
各位  他看上去不妙
Guys, he's not looking so good.
等等
Wait a minute.
"玩
"Play...
否则
or...
就死"
die."
天呐  太变态了
Oh, man. This is so twisted.
谢天谢地
Oh, thank God.
快点  快点
Hurry, hurry, hurry.
准备好了吗
Okay, ready?
你做了什么
What did you do to him?
没什么  我就是...
Nothing. I just put...
是剧毒
It says it's poison.
什么
What?
这不...
That's not...
"拯救就在其中"
"Salvation lies within."
拯...撒谎
Sa-- lies.
是个骗局
It was a trick.
好了  好了
Okay, okay.
解开他的领子  让他呼吸
Just open up his collar so he can breathe.
那是什么
What is that?
我们现在怎么办
So what the hell are we supposed to do now?
我不知道
I don't know.
你说得对
You were right.
幕后黑手不打算杀了我们
Whoever's behind this isn't gonna kill us.
他希望我们互相残杀
He wants us to kill each other.
我...这上面还有一则线索
I... There's another clue right here.
"时间不够了
"Time has run out.
两个是解药
" 2-will cure.
一个将致命"
1-will kill."
那么这附近
Okay, so that has to mean
肯定有解药
that there's a-an antidote around here somewhere.
到处找找  各位  到处找找
Look around. Guys, look around. Look around.
我们找什么
What are we looking for?
这附近有什么东西
Something around here.
"两个是解药"  什么意思啊
"2-will cure"... What does that mean?
还有一个注射器吗
Is it another injector?
"一个将致命"
"1-will kill..."
是针吗
Is it a needle?
各位  我有发现
Hey, guys, found something.
"两个[2]是解药"
"2-will cure."
撑住  伙计
Hang in there, buddy.
这是二号
This is number 2.
我们给他2号就行
We just got to give him number 2.
等等  不对
Wait, wait, no, wait, wait.
不对劲
Something's not right.
这太简单了
Um, it's too easy, too, uh,...
但线索不就是这么说的吗
But that's what the clue said.
"两个是解药"
"2-will cure."
如果意思是
What if that means
两个针剂合用是解药呢
a combination of two vials makes the antidote?
你说什么呢
What are you talking about?
显然我们不能对线索想当然
Well, clearly we can't take any of these clues for granted.
"时间不够了"  这什么意思
"Time has run out"... What does that mean?
钟
Okay, the clock...
那台钟停了
that clock has stopped.
这就是"时间不够了[停止了]"
Which is "Time has run out,"
指针指的是1和3
and the hands are at 1:00 and 3:00,
那么  如果解药是
so what if the antidote...
1和3合起来呢
1 and 3 vials combined.
天呐
Oh, man...
这对吗
I don't know.
你确定吗
You sure about this?
谢天谢地
Oh, thank God.
你没事吧
You all right?
呼吸
Just breathe.
Breathe.
好了  为什么找我来
Okay. Why the hell am I here?
巴克利先生
Well, Mr. Buckley,
我们得知你跟艾玛·马修斯有些问题
we understand that you had some issues with Emma Matthews.
我不知道你什么意思
I don't know what you're talking about.
我喜欢艾玛
I liked Emma.
她的遭遇太可惜了
It's a real shame what happened to her.
是啊  你肯定心都碎了
Yeah, we're sure you're heartbroken,
尤其据说她还散布谣言
especially after she supposedly lied
害你没能在单位得到重要晋升
and beat you out of that big promotion at work.
现在艾玛死了
And now that Emma's dead,
新工作肯定属于你了
that new job is yours for the taking.
等等
Hold on.
我或许并不为艾玛的死感到遗憾
I may not be shedding tears over Emma's demise,
但我也没杀她
but I didn't kill her.
你有一辆白色拉姆350货车  是吧  巴克利先生
You own a white Ram 350 van, don't you, Mr. Buckley?
是啊  怎么了
Yeah. So?
艾玛遇害时
So a van matching that description
有人在她家外面
was seen outside Emma's place
见到了符合这一特征的车
during the time she was murdered.
你昨晚9点到11点间在哪
Where were you between 9:00 and 11:00 last night?
布鲁克林的奥马利酒吧
At O'Malley's Pub in Brooklyn.
我的车就停在外面
And my van was parked right out front.
随便问那里的任何人
Ask anyone there.
我们会的
We will.
最好属实
And it better check out.
告诉你们
And just so you guys know,
艾玛的确说了关于我不实的话才得到了晋升
Emma did lie about me to get that promotion.
那小妞经常说谎
That chick lied all the time.
你说什么呢
What are you talking about?
昨天  我还撞见她在剪辑室
Just yesterday I caught her in the edit bay
数字化老录像带
digitizing old VHS tapes.
艾玛说是一则报道的证据
Emma said it was proof for a story,
但她在做的报道我都知道
but I know all the stories she was working on,
那些视频跟那些报道毫无关系
and those videos had nothing to do with any of them.
艾玛的同事不是说
Wait, didn't Emma's co-worker
她发现了什么证据吗
say she just stumbled on some sort of proof?
巴克利  带子上是什么内容
Buckley, what was on those tapes?
最新美剧下载
www.ZiMuZu.tv
一段奇怪的家庭录影  几个孩子
They were weird home videos of a couple of kids
坐在那里  戴着奇怪的勋章
sitting around wearing these strange medallions.
怎么奇怪
Strange how?
我说不清
I don't know.
圆圆的符号
They... They had round symbols.
这样的吗
Did they look anything like this?
对  就是这样的
Yeah. Exactly like that.
她在数字化的这些录像带有副本吗
Are there copies of these VHS tapes she was digitizing?
嗯  系统会自动把原始影像
Yeah. The system automatically archives the raw footage
备份到服务器
to the server for backup.
你感觉如何
How you feeling?
好多了  谢谢你救了我
Better. Thanks for saving me.
我都不知道你的名字呢
Hey, I don't even know your name.
是啊
That's right.
我们还没好好介绍过
We haven't done proper introductions.
-我是里克  -托德
- I'm Rick. Todd.
我叫西蒙
Yeah, my name's Simon.
犹大
Judah.
各位
Well, gentlemen,
显然  我们被带来是有原因的
um, clearly we were all brought here for a reason.
或许如果我们能想明白是什么原因  就能出去了
Maybe if we can figure out what it is, it'll be our way out.
好吧  怎么想
Okay. How do we do that?
我们跟彼此肯定有某种联系
Well, we all must have some sort of connection to each other.
但我这辈子
Yeah, but I've never seen
从没见过你们任何一个
any of you guys in my life, ever.
是啊  但或许这联系
Right, but it may be some connection
我们尚不了解
we're not yet aware of.
我是个悬疑作家
Um, I'm a mystery writer.
你们是做什么的
What do you guys do for a living?
三年级老师
I'm a third-grade teacher.
牧师
I'm a minister.
-拳击馆老板  -好吧
- I own a boxing gym. - Okay. All right.
没什么关联  你们是哪人
No connection there, but, uh, where are you from?
我是纽约市土生土长的
I'm born and raised in New York City.
悬疑作家  没人在乎我们为什么在这儿
Hey, mystery writer, no one cares why we're here.
我们只想出去
We only care about getting out.
-我同意  -我也是
- I'm with him. - Me too.
这里肯定有什么东西我们能用来逃跑
There's got to be something in here we can use to escape.
那个  犹大
You know what, Judah,
我们上次打破了一样东西时
the last time we broke something,
托德差点丧命
Todd nearly died.
哥们  可不是我给他注射了
Hey, pal, I'm not the one who injected him
毒药  好吗
with poison, okay?
我就是这个意思
That's exactly my point.
到处乱翻
Rummaging around
或许会不慎启动另一个死亡陷阱
may inadvertently activate another deadly trap.
-我们总得做点什么  -同意
- We got to do something. - Agreed.
所以我们放聪明点吧
So let's be smart about it.
密码筒
Um, the cryptex...
让我们发现了毒药
I-It led us to the poison,
毒药让我们发现了解药
and the poison led us to the antidote.
是啊  但解药上面没有线索
Yeah, but there was no clue on the antidote.
钟也是谜底的一部分
The clock was part of that solution.
或许
Maybe...
它有下一个线索
it holds the next clue.
"钥匙能释放你们"
"The key will release you."
什么钥匙
But what key?
阿丽克西斯  你父亲呢
Alexis, where is your father?
他没跟你在一起吗
He's not with you?
如果是那样  我还会问吗
If he were, would I be asking you where he is?
抱歉  抱歉
Okay, sorry, sorry.
不是有意那么冲的
I don't mean to get so bitchy.
只是你父亲没去参加我安排的
It's just that your father blew off that meeting
跟潜在客户的见面
I set up with potential clients.
他今早临时安排了
He had an impromptu get-together
跟史蒂芬·金的见面  或许他还没走
this morning with Stephen King... maybe he's still there.
-你有金的号码吗  -没有
- Do you have King's number? - No.
但他的助理给我爸打了电话
But his assistant called my Dad's cell,
而电话是与办公室电脑相连的
which is linked to the office computer.
好了  这是他的电话记录
Okay, here's his call log.
知道了
Got it.
抱歉  此号码...
We're sorry, you have reached a number...
不通
It's disconnected.
我肯定是打错了
I must have misdialed.
抱歉  此号码...
We're sorry, you have reached a number...
不对劲
Something's wrong.
嗯  史蒂芬·金的新推文
Yeah, there's a new tweet from Stephen King...
"20分钟后看澳大利亚直播节目《晚7点企划》
"Watch me live on Australia's '7PM Project'
有我出镜"
in 20 minutes."
如果史蒂芬·金在澳大利亚
If Stephen King is in Australia...
那我爸在哪
where's my Dad?
"钥匙能释放你们"  什么钥匙啊
"The key will release you," but what key?
或许是比喻
Maybe it's a metaphor.
或许你是个白痴
Maybe you're an idiot.
你能不能闭上嘴  让大人好好思考
Now, will you please shut up so the grown-ups can think?
各位  吵嘴对我们没有帮助
Guys, the bickering is not gonna help us.
或许这屋里有什么东西
Maybe there's something in this room
跟这个钥匙孔是一个形状
that's shaped like this keyhole.
我在哪见过这个形状的
Yeah, I know I've seen that shape before.
伙计们  我们能出去了
Boys, we're getting out of here.
拜托
Oh, come on.
"最后剩下的人将得到自由"
"The last one standing will be freed."
三颗子弹  我们四个人
Three bullets, four of us.
怎么
So, what?
杀了其他人的人就可以走了吗
Whoever kills the others goes free?
把枪给我  里克
Give me the gun, Rick.
不不  把枪给我
No, no, no. I want the gun!
你俩  够了
Both of you, stop!
停下
Stop it.
否则  幕后黑手就要赢了  你们不明白吗
If you don't, whoever's behind this wins, don't you see?
你还不明白我们别无选择吗
Don't you see we're powerless in here?
不是的
No, we're not.
我们可以不玩
We have the power not to play.
听到了吗
You hear that?
我不要再玩你的变态游戏了
We're not gonna play your sick, little game anymore.
你输了
You lose.
是另一个房间
It's another room.
跟这个一样
It's identical to this one.
梅多
Meadow.
我妻子怎么在那里
What's my wife doing in there?
那是我女朋友  帕蒂
That's my girlfriend, Patty.
是一模一样的
It's exactly the same.
一切都一模一样
Everything's the same.
卡塞尔
Castle?
你听得到吗
Do you hear me?
卡塞尔
Castle?
那是我丈夫  西蒙
That was my husband, Simon.
还有我的男友
And my boyfriend.
这也刚好解释了他们手机发来
Which explains the text that they used
引我们到这里的短信
to lure us here.
幕后黑手先劫持了他们
They must have been abducted first
然后用他们的手机给我们发短信
and then their phones were used to text us.
但为什么
But why?
更重要的是  谁是那第四个人
More importantly, who's that fourth man?
什么
What?
对  屏幕上有四个人
Yeah, there were four guys on that screen
但咱们这只有三个
but only three of us.
那个本该出现
What happened to the woman
在这张椅子上的女人出了什么事
that was supposed to be in that chair?
你脖子上是什么
What is that on your neck?
什么
What?
这是什么
What is it?
你也有一个
You have one, too.
我呢
What about me?
没有
No.
那这是好事还是坏事
Well, is that a good thing or a bad thing?
我不知道  但要紧的是保持冷静
I don't know, but the important thing here is to stay calm.
去你的冷静
Screw calm!
我说咱们打碎玻璃  把这里砸开出去
I say we break that glass and hack our way out of here.
-不  那不是好主意  -谁管你
- No, that's not a good idea. - Tough.
如果这不是紧急情况  我不晓得什么还算
If this isn't an emergency, I don't know what is.
听着  幕后黑手无论是谁  都不会
Look, whoever is behind this isn't stupid enough
蠢到给我们留下能够破门而出的工具
to leave something that we can use to go free,
就是说那是个陷阱
which means that's a trap.
现在还是完成这个谜题  看看会发生什么
Now let's just finish this puzzle and see what happens.
好吧
Fine.
你们尽情玩吧
Knock yourself out.
这里有些很熟悉的感觉
Something about this feels familiar.
什么意思
What do you mean?
同样的房间  任务
Identical rooms, the tasks --
我在研究生院时读过一则案例
in grad school I read a case study
检验在压力环境下的分离焦虑
that examines separation anxiety in stressful situations.
这块当然是压力环境
Well, this certainly is stressful.
谢天谢地
Oh. Thank God.
你在干嘛
What are you doing?
抽根烟  我遭了罪  还不享受一下
Having a smoke. I think I've earned it.
不行
No!
我告诉过你  你不能相信这地方的所有东西
I told you -- you can't trust anything in this place.
可能会杀死你
This could kill you.
这是香烟
It's a cigarette.
当然最终会害死我
It's definitely gonna kill me eventually.
这又是什么
What the hell is that?
闻起来像花生
It smells like peanuts.
我对花生过敏
I'm allergic.
看起来贝克特警监
Looks like Captain Beckett
救了你一命
just saved your life.
你开始团队合作  好吗
So how about you start being a team player?
我要你来告诉我
I need you to tell me
有关那个案例的所有事情
everything you can about this study.
我老婆在哪里干啥  还有你们的
What the hell is my wife doing in here, and yours?
他们一定是人质
They must be leverage
为了逼迫我们服从命令  否则她们可能受伤害
to make us follow the rules or else they get hurt.
或者我们是人质
Or maybe we're the leverage.
那托德呢
And what about Todd?
他在那边谁也没有
He didn't have anyone in that room.
他是个神父  是独身者
He's a priest. They're celibate.
我是牧师  规矩不同的
I'm a minister. The rules are different.
所以有位牧师太太  但不在里面
So is there a Mrs. Minister that's not in there?
不  但这不意味着
No, but that doesn't mean
没有我在乎的人
there aren't people I care about.
如果他们中任何人出了事
And if something happened to one of them --
我们不确知
Look, we don't know enough
你需要担心的这些  好吗
for you to be worried about that, okay?
老天  锁在在房间里  一只装了子弹的手枪
Ah, hell, being locked in this room with a loaded gun
让相互杀戮的指示
and instructions to kill one another
足够让我担心了
is plenty to be worried about.
我们不会那么做的
We're not gonna do that.
我们要做的是想明白
What we should be doing is figuring out
为什么我们会在这里
why the hell we're here.
还有为什么有些人被打上那种标志
And why are some of us marked with this symbol
另些人没有
and others aren't.
女人中有人有那标志吗
Did you see the symbol on any of the women?
我看到派翠西脖子上有东西  但我没有
I saw something on Patricia's neck, but I don't have one.
-你老婆呢  -没有
- And what about your wife? - No.
你确定
You sure?
我眼睛没有离开过她
I didn't take my eyes off of her.
所以她没有而你有
So she doesn't have one but you do.
根据这个规律  贝克特一定有
Following that pattern, Beckett must have one
因为我没有
because I don't.
什么意思
Meaning what?
如果有标志的人
Well, what if the people with the symbol
是重要的目标  其他人只是人质
are the important ones and the rest of us are leverage?
他在那里
There he is.
他在那里做什么
What's he doing in there?
等一下  那辆货车什么情况
Wait, what's going on with that van?
到底出了什么事
Uh, what the hell just happened?
那是我爸爸吗
Was that my dad?
所以巴克利送来了
So, Buckley sent over those tapes
艾玛转换过的录像带
that Emma was digitizing.
然后
And?
他是对的
Well, he's right.
很奇怪
It's, uh, weird.
他们在干嘛
What are they doing?
解谜题  持续多个小时
Solving puzzles. For hours.
他们戴着那个标识  像巴克利所说的
And they're wearing the symbol, just like Buckley said.
那个小女孩是艾玛吗
Could that little girl be Emma?
有可能
It's possible.
根据衣着和图像质量
Based on clothing and picture quality,
实验室认为录像带最少是20年前的
the lab thinks that the tape is at least 20 years old.
如果是爱玛  那小男孩是谁
If it is Emma, then who's that little boy
这些录像带和她被谋杀有什么关系
and what do these videos have to do with her murder?
我害怕
I'm scared.
我再不想玩这个游戏了
I don't want to play this game anymore.
求求你  让我出去
Please, let me out.
老爸丢了  我们也联系不到贝克特的手机
Dad's missing and we can't reach Beckett's cell.
打住  打住
Whoa, whoa, whoa. Hold on, hold on.
贝克特在一个法医会议上  阿丽克西斯
Beckett's at a forensics conference, Alexis.
不  她没有出现
No. She never showed.
里奇今早被引进了一栋空楼
Rick was lured into an empty building this morning.
我黑进了邻近街边的摄像头
I hacked a nearby street camera and got footage
发现一辆白色货车逃离现场
of a white van fleeing the scene.
邻居看到艾玛家门前停了辆白色货车
Neighbors saw a white van in front of Emma's building.
艾玛是谁
Who's Emma?
谋杀案被害人
A murder victim.
我们认为杀害她的凶手
We think her killer
也许开着一辆生锈的白色货车
might have been have been driving a rusty white van.
如果线索是正确的  那么这一定就是钥匙
If the clue is right, this must be the key.
我收回对你所有的冷言恶语
I take back every bad thing i've been thinking about you.
是吗  谢了
Yeah, well, thank you.
又是一个智力游戏
Just another mind game.
"最后剩下的人将得到自由"
"The last one standing will be freed."
两发子弹
Two bullets.
三个人
And three of us.
很显然抓我们的人想让我们自相残杀
Clearly our captor's trying to turn us against each other.
这是什么变态的新考验
What kind of sick new test is this?
我不知道  不过它似乎不那么复杂
I don't know, but it seems a little unsophisticated.
梅多
Meadow!
你在干什么
What are you doing?
这叫做适者生存
It's called survival of the fittest.
还是混凝土
Just more concrete.
归在"意料之中"类别
Which falls under the "To be expected" column.
不
Oh, no.
对不起  哥们
Sorry, boys.
我妻子做得对
My wife's got the right idea.
梅多  你不必这么做
Meadow, you don't have to do this.
听着  这无关个人感情
Look, it's nothing personal.
把枪给我  梅多
Give me the gun, Meadow.
杀了我们并不能让你从这里出去
Shooting us isn't gonna get you out of here any faster.
很抱歉  但不是你死就是我亡
I'm sorry, but it's you or me.
西蒙
Simon...
杀了我们并不会让那道门打开
shooting us is not gonna get that door open.
你又不知道
You don't know that.
字条上说只有一个人能幸存
The note says only one will survive.
我得让那个人是我
I need to make sure it's me.
别走上这条绝路
Don't go down this path.
抱歉  牧师
Sorry, Preacher.
他死了
He's dead.
枪管被封死了
The barrel is sealed.
这把枪就像这房间一样被动过手脚
The gun's as rigged as this room.
戴真手铐之前先用这个吧
Until I get you into real handcuffs.
拜托
Come on.
我们不能握手言和吗
Can't we work something out?
你想杀了我们
You tried to kill us.
如果她没把子弹取出来
If she hadn't taken the bullets out,
你就动手了
you would have.
我那时候已经不是自己了
I wasn't myself.
战逃反应  纯粹是动物本能
It was fight or flight, pure animal instinct.
不  西蒙
No. Simon.
我非常抱歉
I'm so sorry.
算了吧
Save it.
你的丈夫杀了他
Your husband killed him.
我们不知道那是不是真的
We don't know that.
离我远点
Get away from me.
我们该怎么做
What are we gonna do?
这对抓我们的人来说就是一场游戏
This is all a game to our captor.
我们在任人摆布
We're being manipulated.
我们要改变规则
We're gonna change the rules.
你有消息的时候打电话给我
Just give me a call whenever you hear something.
有线索了
Hey. I got something.
维克拉姆仔细排查了录像
Vikram scrubbed the footage.
他发现一个智力玩具下方写着
He found the name "Northcliff"
"诺斯克利夫"这个名字
written at the bottom of one of the puzzles.
艾玛十几岁的时候
Now, when Emma was a teenager,
她曾经替一对精神病专家夫妻遛狗
she walked dogs for a pair of psychiatrists --
乔福瑞·诺斯克利夫和萨曼莎·诺斯克利夫
Geoffrey and Samantha Northcliff.
进展不错
This is good.
更好的在后面
Yeah, and it gets better.
艾玛被谋杀的前晚
There was a break-in at the Northcliffs' apartment
诺斯克利夫夫妇的公寓遭到了入室偷窃
the night before Emma was murdered.
警方报告表明
According to the police report,
唯一丢失的私人物品
only personal property was taken.
VHS录像带
The VHS tapes.
一定是她闯进去偷那些录像带的
She must have broken in to steal them.
但是为什么
But why?
我们去问问诺斯克利夫夫妇
Let's ask the Northcliffs.
我找不到他们
I can't find them.
但是我把他们的秘书带到审讯室了
But I've got their secretary in the box right now.
很好
All right.
真是一场悲剧
So much tragedy.
我在艾玛十几岁之后就再也没见过她了
I hadn't seen Emma since she was a teenager.
然后上周我在费耶的葬礼上遇到了她
And then I ran into her last week at Fay's funeral.
谁的葬礼
Whose funeral?
费耶·诺斯克利夫
Fay Northcliff --
乔福瑞和萨曼莎的女儿
Geoffrey and Samantha's daughter.
她发生了什么
What happened to her?
她上吊自杀了
She hung herself.
可怜的孩子
The poor girl.
她有什么兄弟姐妹吗
Did she have any siblings?
有一个双胞胎弟弟  布兰登
Yes. A twin brother, Brandon.
-这两个人是你说的双胞胎吗  -是的
- And are these the twins, right here? - Yes.
25年前  诺斯克利夫夫妻在
25 years ago, the Northcliffs did groundbreaking research
儿童的分离焦虑方面有突破性研究
on separation anxiety in children.
但当时有传言研究中存在不道德行为
But there were rumors of unethical behavior.
他们参与到了一些
And they were involved in some
非常边缘化的行为科学之中
pretty fringe behavioral science.
诺斯克利夫夫妇是不是用他们的亲生孩子做了测试对象
Did the Northcliffs use their own children as test subjects?
我什么都不知道
I wouldn't know anything about that.
艾玛死了 罗丝
Emma's dead, Rose.
如果是她闯进诺斯克利夫夫妇的公寓
And if she broke into the Northcliffs' apartment
去偷那些录像带
to steal those tapes,
那她就是准备揭发他们
then she was planning to expose them.
那么很有可能是诺斯克利夫夫妇
It's possible that the Northcliffs
杀了她封口
killed her to keep that secret.
如果你不想作为从犯被起诉
And if you don't want to be charged as an accessory,
你现在最好老实交代
then you better come clean right now.
你们得相信我
You have to believe me.
我不知道那些实验
I didn't know the experiments
会伤害那些孩子
were doing harm to those children.
但是时间说明了一切
Time has proven otherwise.
布兰登逃离了这个国家  成了一个隐士
Brandon fled the country, became a recluse.
可怜的费耶  你们知道她的结局
Poor Fay -- you know what happened to her.
你知道诺斯克利夫夫妇现在可能在哪里吗
Do you have any idea where the Northcliffs might be right now?
我从昨天起就没再见过他们
I haven't seen them since yesterday.
我发誓
I swear to you.
伙计们
Guys.
海莉查到了那辆货车的下落
Hayley ID'd the van.
车登记在一个名叫乔福瑞·诺斯克利夫
It's registered to a professional corporation
所属的职业公司名下
owned by somebody named Geoffrey Northcliff.
他和他妻子是我们的头号嫌疑人
He and his wife are our prime suspects.
你查到了注册地址吗
Did you get an address of the registration?
查到了  哈茨戴尔郊外的一处隐秘住宅
Yes, it's a secluded property outside Hartsdale.
那也许是他们扣留卡塞尔和贝克特的地方
That could be where they're holding Castle and Beckett.
-我们走吧  -好
- Let's go. - Yeah.
这样行不通
This is not gonna happen.
我们得再精明点
We need to work smarter.
怎么办
How?
这扇门是唯一的出路
That door's the only way out.
要是我们能找到可以当做杠杆的东西
If we could find something we can use as a pry bar,
我们就能够伸到锁和门框之间
we can get it between lock and the frame,
这样也许可以把门撬开
we might be able to pop it open.
好的
Yeah, okay.
好吧
All right.
这里面的化学物质都是易爆的
So, the chemicals in there are explosive.
只要一个催化剂就能把它引爆
It just needs a catalyst to set it off.
很好
Great.
导火索
Fuse.
给你
There you go.
谢谢  太好了
Thanks. Perfect.
我一直都很喜欢这东西的味道
I've always loved the smell of this stuff.
好了
Okay.
你俩最好躲起来
You two better hide.
那是什么
What was that?
不知道  但我们得赶紧离开这
I don't know, but we need to get out of here now.
好的
Okay.
跟紧
Just stay close.
这可能是另一个陷阱
This could be another trap.
退后
Get back.
那里有人  跟紧点  好吗
There's someone there. Stay close, okay?
别开枪
Don't shoot.
那是用来杀掉开枪者的
It's rigged to kill the shooter.
西蒙就是那样死的
That's how Simon died.
谢天谢地你没事
Thank God you're okay.
帕特里夏
Patricia.
你还好吗
You okay?
是的  没事
Yeah. Good.
我们得继续走
We should keep moving.
他说得对
He's right.
这有可能是个陷阱
It could be a trap!
不  等等
No, wait, wait.
没事
It's fine!
我们可以出去了
W-We can get out.
我们走  赶紧离开这
Let's go. Let's get out of here.
总算可以走了
About damn time.
我们自由了
Oh, we're free!
不
No!
-不  -我们被困在里面了
- No! - We're locked in.
不管他们出于什么目的
Whatever they're for,
我们只有不到五分钟的时间来想明白了
we got less than five minutes to figure it out.
门一锁死  倒计时就开始了
It started counting down as soon as the doors closed.
明显这房间是抓我们的人设计的终局
Okay, clearly this room is our captor's endgame.
他想让我们最后困在这里
He wanted us to end up here.
为什么  他想从我们身上得到什么
Why? What does he want from us?
是另一条线索吗
Another clue?
谜题的最后一部分
Last piece of the puzzle --
剩下的人
"Of those who remain,
只有你们的另一半可以活着
only your better half can survive."
这到底是什么意思
What the hell does that mean?
这里有六个人  三个控制杆
There are six of us left and three levers.
他想把爱人分开
He wants to separate the couples,
让我们来选择谁可以获得自由
make us choose who goes free.
留下的人要拉动控制杆
And who stays behind to pull the levers.
我猜三个杆子必须同时拉动
I assume all three need to be pulled at once
才能把门打开
to open the door.
除非他就想让我们这么去想
Unless that's what he wants us to think.
这三个控制杆也可能把房间炸毁
These levers could just as easily blow this room.
我们怎么知道呢
How are we supposed to know?
我们必须要有信念
We have to have faith.
等等
W-Wait, wait!
看到了吗  信念
See? Faith.
现在  谁愿意和我留在这
Now, who's staying in here with me?
州警察
State police!
我们找到了两名人质
We got two hostages!
是诺斯克利夫夫妇
It's the Northcliffs.
-卧室安全  -厨房安全
-Bedroom's clear! -Kitchen's clear!
这是什么
What the hell is this?
爸爸
Dad?
他们在哪里
Where are they?
山脚下的树林里有一个隐蔽的房子
There's a building hidden in the trees at the bottom of the hill.
是谁做的  谁把你们留在这里
Who's behind this? Who left you here?
我们的儿子布兰登
Our son, Brandon.
我们快没时间了
We're out of time.
你们必须做出选择
You need to choose which ones of you
谁要和我一起留在这里
are staying in here with me.
我留下
I'll stay.
卡塞尔
Castle.
好吧
Fine.
我不会把你单独留在这的
But I'm not letting you stay here alone.
帕特里夏你带着其他人走
Patricia, you leave with the others.
指示上说了"你们的另一半"
The instructions say "Your better half."
如果你俩都留下  这就破坏了规则
If you both stay, that's breaking the rules.
去他的规则
Screw the rules!
这样对所有人都会造成不好的后果
There could be consequences for all of us!
我们服从规则也会有后果
There's consequences when we follow the rules, too.
没事
Come on.
谢谢你
Thank you!
我们会去求救的
We'll send help.
现在怎么办
So, what now?
对不起
I'm sorry.
我以为我们可以跑出去
I thought we could run out the door.
真的吗
Really?
不是因为我们打破了你的规则吗
So it's not because we broke your rules?
他确实说了会有后果
Well, he did say that there would be consequences.
我们知道是你搞的鬼
We know it's you.
该死
Damn it.
别动
Don't!
我哪里露馅了
What gave me away?
即便我们认为这房间是险境
When you ran into this room,
你还是跑进来了
even though we all suspected it would be booby-trapped.
还有当你拉动控制杆时
And then when you pulled that lever,
你一点都没犹豫
you didn't even hesitate.
就跟西蒙扣动扳机时
Same way you didn't hesitate
你没有犹豫一样
when Simon pulled the trigger.
你不害怕
You weren't afraid,
不是因为你是有信仰的牧师
and not because you're a "minister" With faith,
而是因为你是幕后黑手
but because you are a mastermind with the knowledge
知道枪被改造  会从后射出
that the gun was rigged to fire backwards.
这把不会
Not like this one.
把实验完成吧
Let's finish the experiment.
你们其中一个得死掉
One of you has to die.
这就是规则
Those are the rules.
你为什么这么做
Why are you doing this?
当我父母把我和双胞胎姐姐分开
That's the same question I asked my parents
没日没夜测试我们时
when they would rip me away from my twin sister --
我问了同样的问题
testing us over and over, day after day.
听着  任何人都不该
Look, no one should be treated
遭受你和姐姐的待遇
the way you and your sister were.
让我们帮你
Let us help you.
帮你  就凭你
Help me? You?
为什么
Why?
因为你是警察
'Cause you're a cop?
我还是孩子的时候  跟警察谈过
I talked to cop once, when I was a kid.
你知道发生了什么吗
You know what happened?
他派了两个12分局的警员去
He sent over two officers from the 12th Precinct,
你的分局
your precinct.
他们跟我父母
They talked to my parents
谈了五分钟  就走掉了
for five minutes, then walked away!
很抱歉
I'm sorry.
抱歉有什么用  我姐姐遭罪了
Not as sorry as my sister was.
我父母命令我们接受更多分离  测试
My parents ordered more isolation, more tests.
你认为贝克特应该为此负责
So you're holding Beckett responsible?
她那时还是个孩子
She was a child when that happened.
你为什么要惩罚她
Why are you punishing her?
这不是惩罚  这是科学
This isn't punishment. This is science.
帕特里夏是教育委员会的心理医生
Patricia is a psychiatrist on the Board of Education.
那里也有人让你和姐姐失望了
Did someone there let you and your sister down?
凯特  所有人都让我们大失所望
Kate, everyone let us down.
这么说  我们是
So we're all surrogates
那些没能保护你们的人的代替品
for people that weren't able to protect you two.
但你很小心地选择了彼此相爱的人
But you were careful to choose people who love each other,
因为你爱你的姐姐
because you loved your sister.
她是你的灵魂伴侣
She was your soulmate.
现在你们其中一个也能感同身受了
Now one of you has to feel what I feel.
为什么选择艾玛
Now, why did you choose Emma?
她想曝光我的父母
She wanted to expose my parents!
那不够
That's not enough --
两个孩子解谜的视频
some video tapes of some kids doing puzzles?
算不上什么  新闻上播播就再无音讯
That's nothing, a blip in the news cycle.
但你们其中一人生还
But one of you goes free,
告诉外界我杀掉了你的挚爱并自杀
and tells how I killed your one true love and myself --
只有那时  世界才会明白我父母制造了
only then will the world truly understand the monster
怎样的怪兽
my parents created.
别多说了
No more talking.
该解决最后的谜题了
Time to solve the final puzzle.
哪个死
Which one of you dies?
我不会选择
I won't choose.
我也不会
Neither will I.
赶紧决定  否则我就打残你们  直到死掉
Decide or I'll start maiming you till someone does.
好吧
Okay, okay.
我选
I'll choose.
I-I'll decide.
很好
Good.
谁死  里克
Who dies, Rick?
谁都不死
No one dies.
别动
Don't move.
你们还好吗
You guys okay?
没事  感谢来营救我们
Yeah. Thanks for rescuing us.
是啊  很显然没了我们你们很无助
Yes, because clearly you're helpless without us.
你们怎么找到我们的
How'd you guys even find us?
我们有最棒的帮手
Well, we had our best person on it.
真是不能让你独处五分钟
I can't leave you alone for five minutes.
难道说不拥抱我了吗
Does this mean no hug?
我出去嗨
I'm heading out for a bit of fun.
一起吗
Want to come with?
不了  多谢邀请
I'll pass. Thanks.
你怎么样
How you doing?
你很担心你的父亲
You worry a lot about your Father.
如果理查德·卡塞尔是你爸  你也会的
You would, too, if Richard Castle was your dad.
他一年也就被绑架两次
I mean, the guy's abducted, like, what, twice a year?
有点超标
I think that's a tad above the national average.
但他总是回家
Yet he always comes home.
你知道为什么吗
Do you know why that is?
知道
Yeah.
他很幸运
He's really lucky.
不  他很擅长他所做的
No. He's really good at what he does.
他有你这么棒吗
Is he as good as you?
当然没有
Good heavens, no.
你为什么会这么问
Why would you ask such a thing?
好了  给你打扮打扮
All right. We're gonna get you dolled up,
我们去夜店
we are gonna go out to some clubs,
闯点小祸
we're gonna get into just a tiny, little bit of trouble.
无伤大雅  走吧
Never hurt anyone. Come on.
谢了
Thanks.
还好吗
You okay?
我在想那些小孩
Yeah, I was just thinking about those little kids.
我是说
I mean...
很多人让他们失望了
a lot of people let them down.
尽管最终他们的父母被曝光
And although their parents are finally being exposed,
远不及弥补一切
it's far too little, too late.
今早醒来  我绝没想到
This is not the day that I was expecting
这一天如此度过
when I woke up this morning.
可不是
Tell me about it.
至少结果还不赖
But at least it's ending well.
是啊
Yeah.
怎么了
What's wrong?
没事
Nothing.
我只是很期待
I-I ju-- I was really looking forward
能够与...
to the prospect of collaborating
史蒂芬·金合作
with Stephen King, you know?
卡塞尔  想想好的一面
Well, you know, Castle, look on the bright side.
史蒂芬·金打来电话时
When Stephen King does call,
至少现在你有个打破尴尬的超赞段子了
at least you'll have one hell of an icebreaker.